projectswole.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Project Swole

ProjectSwole.com (“Project Swole”) recognizes that its visitors, members, users, and others who use the website at www.ProjectSwole.com (the “Project Swole website”), (collectively or individually you, your, “Users”) value their privacy. This Privacy Notice provides important information about the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Project Swole website. Project Swole provides this Privacy Notice to help you understand what information Project Swole collects and how that information will be used.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Project Swole Terms of Use. Your use of the Project Swole website and any personal information you provide on the Project Swole website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

By participating, using or viewing the Project Swole website or any content thereof, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of these terms, then please do not use the Project Swole website or its Content. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Your continued use of the Project Swole website following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept those changes. If you have any questions or comments about the Project Swole privacy policy, please contact us.

### The Information Collected by Project Swole

Information Provided by You: You provide personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Project Swole when you become a member of the Project Swole community and other information by choosing to participate in various activities on the Project Swole website (such as creating polls, posting comments or messages, participating in discussions, etc.).

Cookies: Use of “Cookies” is standard in the Internet industry. Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters that are sent to your computer and uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving passwords, and preferences while you’re at a website. When you visit the Project Swole website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer. Some cookies are temporary and will disappear after you close your browser, but others will stay on your computer. If you wish to remove cookies from your hard drive, follow your web browser’s help file directions. You can also reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Project Swole website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Traffic Data: When you use the Project Swole website, our servers automatically log certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. This information may include information such as your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Tracking Usage Patterns: Project Swole tracks usage patterns and collects other non-personally-identifiable information about use of the Project Swole website. We may employ various tracking technology including “clear GIFs” (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users (in a way that does not collect or disclose personally-identifiable information), and clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to you to track which emails are opened by recipients.

### The Way Project Swole Uses Information

Personally identifiable information that you submit to us through the Project Swole website, will be used by Project Swole to provide to you the features and functionality of the Project Swole website and to operate and maintain the Project Swole website.

Any personal information, text or other content that you voluntarily provide in the course of your use of the Project Swole website, including but not limited to, information in your Member Profile, by participating in polls, discussions, comments and communities, is publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your User Name (but not your email address) is displayed to other Users in connection with the polls you create and messages you post in discussions. Any information that you post on the Project Swole website may be redistributed through the internet and may be viewed by the general public. We will not sell or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties. However, Project Swole may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial and marketing messages, and market research related surveys and other offers to you. You have an opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of any such programs by sending an e-mail to info@projectswole.com with the term “BLOCK” (in all caps) in the subject line. We will also use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Project Swole website changes or for customer service purposes).

We will also use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as usage data, server log information, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, other technical data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Project Swole website and to create new features, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

We use cookies, “clear GIFs”, and log file information to: (a) to assist with your use of the website by “remembering” information so that you will not have to re-enter it during subsequent visits to the Project Swole website; (b) provide customized, personalized content and information for you; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics (such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.); and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

### When Project Swole Discloses Information

We will not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as traffic information and usage tracking information) with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Project Swole website.

We may provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons in connection with the limited purpose of outsourcing of technical functions. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We reserve the right to release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

Project Swole also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that Project Swole believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions to avoid liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Project Swole, our Users or others.

### Your Options

You may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Project Swole website, but if you do, certain aspects of the Project Swole experience will not be available to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting the Controls section on the My Dashboard page. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access, or making corrections, to your profile. It is your responsible to maintain the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

### Advertising Policy, Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Project Swole allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Project Swole website. These advertisements fund the Project Swole site and it’s operation. It is important to note that they have no influence over the content of Project Swole and that we have placed descriptive text near all advertisements, clearly labeled with the words “Advertisement” or “Ads By.”

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Project Swole website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies or other tracking technologies) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Project Swole does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if you respond to any advertisements, the advertiser or ad-server may collect certain information about you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Project Swole’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

Data Security Project Swole uses commercially reasonable safeguards (physical, managerial, and technical) to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Project Swole and you transmit any such information at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Project Swole makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If Project Swole learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

### Childrens’ Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Project Swole does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information on the Project Swole website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Project Swole website at any time or in any manner. If Project Swole learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Project Swole website without verified parental consent, then Project Swole will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### International Users

The Project Swole website is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Project Swole website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Project Swole website, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### Changes to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised from time to time and this will be reflected by the “effective date” below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we use your personal information only in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Project Swole website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

Date Last Modified: November 12, 2008.
